Who is that?
This girl is Jolyne Kujo, but where
in God's name is Lang Wrangler?
Am I right to assume that
he failed his objective
and she still has the
disc in her possession?
If so, within a few moments,
she will meet someone at the courtyard
and hand the disc off to them.
I know that guy.
He serves as a priest
at the prison's chapel.
What is he doing here?
Did she find out?
No.
If she had any inkling
that I was her enemy,
we would be in the midst
of battle right now.
Hold on! Father, wait!
I beg of you, whatever you do,
please don't sound that alarm!
The last thing that I want here is to
cause trouble or make some kind of scene!
What do I do?
Should I take the chance
and knock him out?
Sure I could, if it's to
bring my old man back to life.
Hitting a priest is nothing.
Aren't you ignoring the
real problem happening here?
You've taken someone else's work permit
card and used it to get me to open the door.
Pray tell what has become of the
prisoner this card actually belongs to,
Lang Wrangler.
I know you just met me, so I won't
ask you to believe what I'm saying.
But I have no reason
to lie to you, Father.
I was assaulted by the prisoner you're
referring to, so I defended myself.
He's in that hamper probably dreaming
about how I knocked him out cold.
Regardless of the reason, I am obligated
to report this matter to the authorities.
Sure, do what you have to.
However, it has to be after
I get to the courtyard.
Give me two minutes.
No, all I need is a single
solitary minute, Father.
Let me go to the courtyard
and you can turn me in.
That's all I ask.
Are you asking me to
overlook your wrongdoings?
Someone's life is on the line.
My own dad's life and spirit.
Surely a priest like yourself
can understand my situation.
Are you by your lonesome?
Or is there anyone else in here with you?
Nuh-uh.
It's only me.
I can't believe I just lied to a priest.
But a tiny lie like that can be forgiven.
and mentioning the disks would
send up immediate red flags.
Please, Father, one minute is all I ask.
In most cases, when someone
does something for others,
they expect to receive some
sort of reward in return.
To be kind to others is to expect that
same kindness from those you give it to,
and that cannot be called
unconditional love.
True unconditional love, my dear,
is the reward of eventually
reaching the gates of heaven.
You may go.
So, I will pretend that our
paths never crossed here.
But per your request,
you only have one minute.
I trust you'll return to this gate
by then and not a second longer.
I had to let her go.
Despite her lie, I know
someone is hiding there.
If she does have comrades around,
I cannot risk revealing
that I am Palesnake's user,
even if it is to dispose of Jolene.
According to the Speedwagon Foundation,
I'll know how to hand over the disc
once I arrive at the courtyard.
I guess this is what they meant.
Hey, you.
Do you have a pass that
permits you to be out here?
I'm gonna say that's a no.
So that must mean you're trying to escape.
What?
What the hell happened?
Sounding the alarm was
never part of my plan.
I'm glad I thought ahead.
Having a guard patrol the
courtyard was the perfect decision.
Let's go.
Fight!
Mode nash no survival day Get away!
I don't wanna see!
No time! Let's get started! Go!
1, 2, 3 Coming right away!
I'm on me! I'm on me!
I'm on me!
Stop!
Break out! Tick up! I'm on me!
I'm on me!
Break out!
Don't stop beating!
Don't stop beating! I'm mad!
In the year 1988 my
life took a turn i met a
man from Egypt who possessed
the ability to stop
time itself and we
developed a rather close
relationship one evening
he suddenly told me this
If someone wished to go to
heaven, there may be a way.
He was young and unbelievably beautiful,
but with an aura about him that suggested
he had lived for hundreds of years.
At that time, I was 16 and a student
aspiring to go to a seminary.
Hey, don't look at me that way.
I'm just talking about the human mind.
It's not like I'm telling
you to wither and die.
This heaven pertains to our spirits
and where they go after death.
Earth.
As your spirit evolves,
so too does your power.
Where they ultimately end up is
what fascinates me.
Surely you of all people
understand what I'm talking about.
It's there that one will
find true happiness.
That is, if they can make
it into heaven, of course.
Though I'm aware, joy cannot be
found by having an invincible body,
vast riches,
or even reigning over all humanity
in the end the true winner is the one
who gets to witness heaven that's why
I will get there someday no matter what
it costs me and how are you going to
achieve that exactly ah well I wrote
the process in a notebook one day find
me in Egypt I'll show it to you there
If I ever hope to figure this
out, I will need you to assist me.
However, before I could learn
the means of attaining Heaven,
the notebook he spoke of was burned to ash
by none other than Jolene Kujo's father,
Jotaro Kujo.
Jotaro laid eyes on the contents
of the notebook that day,
and with the book gone, the information
was sealed with him forever.
Along with the man who aimed
for heaven, Dio Brando himself.
For the next 20 years, I waited patiently
for my chance to obtain Jotaro's memories,
so that I could relive the
moment that he read the notebook.
And finally, after decades, I got it.
His memories were mine, along with the stand
that surpassed even Dio, Star Platinum.
I ensured that Jotaro's
body would wither and decay.
And although his troublesome daughter
behaved in ways I never could have expected,
it's all taken care of now.
What?
She got shot?
Jolene got shot? But by who? A guard?
Or maybe that bastard Pale
Snake figured out where she was
going to deliver the disc and
he's hiding around here somewhere.
JOLENE!
The Guard and Control will take
care of retrieving Star Platinum,
so there's no reason for
me to stay here anymore.
With that out of the way, I
should head back to the chapel.
Hm?
What was I doing out here again?
Oh right, the disc.
I was given orders to bring this
thing back without a scratch on it.
And I was also ordered to make sure
Jolene Cujoh was finished off for good.
Thing is, I don't know
who gave me these orders.
I can't seem to remember.
Doesn't matter. Either way,
I was given orders to completely blast
straight through Jolene's head with this gun.
Damn it all.
Well, there's nothing I
can do to help you now.
In your greatest moment of
need, I'm utterly useless.
It's over now, Jolene Kujo!
What the hell?!
My weather forecast is a
power to control the weather.
At this point, this is all I can offer.
Jolene, I wasn't able to save you, but
I might be able to protect the disk.
And if you still have the strength
within you to keep fighting,
you may be able to survive.
Between the years of 1887 and 1974 in the
state of Florida alone
there were more than
50 reported cases of fish frogs snakes and
sheep falling from the sky in unbelievable
numbers it was caused by a tornado at least
that's what they say and these colorful
amphibians are poison dart frogs that live
on treetops in Central and South America.
They carry a deadly poison
under their skin that
aboriginal Americans
used for their blowguns.
What the actual fuck is going on here?
This is judging by the
color of these frogs' skin.
They're most certainly poison dart frogs.
It takes less than a few seconds for
the poison to get inside the body,
causing the heart and
respiratory system to stop.
That's the bodily fluid that's being
splattered all over the place right now.
Halesnake!
But this power, could it be his
ability to control the weather?
Weather forecast.
He's supposed to have lost his memory.
Was he the one hiding behind the oil drum?
I must go.
Where's the card key?
Not good.
The frog's fluid is
soaking into my thread.
Someone!
If somebody can hear me, open the gate!
Anyone!
Calm down.
Maintain your peace of mind.
What should I do at a time like this?
Two. Three. Five.
I must stay calm.
Count prime numbers to
compose my thoughts.
Prime numbers are lonely numbers that can
only be divided by one and themselves.
It gives me courage 23
28 no it's 29 damn it
the filthy frogs are
clean to my 800 pants?
Weather forecast is at
the laundry room he's too
far I can't make him stop
these frogs from Raining
down escape is my only
viable option 41 yes
that's right the guard
that was at the Courtyard?
What happened to him?
Is he still under my control? Hello?
Can you hear me?
Guard, are you there?
Get back in here.
That is a direct order!
I need your help, Father!
Please help me!
Please beg God to spare
my soul from this hell!
43, 47, 53, 59.
The Poison One.
I'm begging you!
Tell the Lord to save me!
Stay calm and listen to my voice!
I need your card key!
Get over here and give it to me quickly!
Could I be saved if I give this to you?
Hey!
Don't take it out while you're over there!
You fool!
67... 71...
What on earth is going on in this place?
All those frogs?
Oh, what a relief.
Please, sir, I need you to
open this gate immediately.
Wait, why are you here, Father?
What's happening?
I have no idea.
A tornado, maybe.
Now please, just hurry.
I understand. Right away.
These frogs are...
What are you standing there for?
We have another guard in
here who's already fallen.
You have to open the gate!
You don't mean he's...
For now, try to remain calm, Father.
I'll go find someone
who can help right away!
Hold on!
Where do you think you're going?
All you have to do is hit the switch
over here and the gate will open!
Yes, I understand that, sir.
But there may be a liability.
So, I need to check with my supervisor.
So, please, just calm down.
I'll be back soon.
Ah, but I am perfectly calm.
The only one who isn't
calm here, 73, 79, is you.
Are you going to abandon me?
I'll be back right away, Father!
Now, Pale Snake, take a disc from
my collection and hand it to me!
I can't control all of them, but
I can choose one to enact my will!
Explode after flying 10 meters!
That's a direct order!
Ah, my eyes, help me, please
call somebody, father.
I need medical attention.
83, 89, 97, if you want
me, I'm right here.
Just open the door.
You must know if I'm able to
leave here and call for help,
you can get treatment right away.
That is what you were thinking, is it not?
If so, why would you not make it a priority
to move in the direction of my voice?
Father!
The disc that contains
Shotaro Kujo Star Platinum.
Exactly what should I do about it now?
I took care of Jolene, but I can't
just leave her in the courtyard.
Did the gate finally open?
Please take me with you!
Who? Father? Hello? Father? Where are you?
This is my limit.
I can't hold back the poison anymore.
And I dropped the disc.
I don't even know where it is.
The rain has stopped but where is
Jolene Kujo's lifeless body if I find her
I should find the disc I was frightened
there for a moment but there's no way
frogs can defeat a snake search for it
palesnake's range of movement is barely
20 meters at best I'm running a huge
risk by even being here if someone sees?
tells me all bets are off,
but there's no other way.
The soul of a deceased criminal
returns to Earth in the form of a frog
in the name of trying to bring its
companions to the land of the dead.
I have heard that in the East there
are stories of a similar nature,
but this horror is truly the
personification of that proverb.
Nonetheless, the disk I seek
must be around here somewhere.
Listen, Pale Snake.
I want you to sweep the area between where
you are and the entrance to the gate.
The guard may have taken it earlier.
It should be in that direction.
Ah, here it is!
I have retrieved the disc.
Thanks a lot.
I've been waiting for
you to find where it was.
This is so gross, they're all over
my face, makes me want to throw up.
The poison only comes out when
the frogs splatter on impact,
so if they don't explode they're harmless.
That's why I made a
net using live frogs in
order to lessen the
impact of the frogs still
falling, which allowed me to lay
in wait for you to locate the disk.
It doesn't matter!
You lost!
Accept your fate and die!
Actually, it was already here.
The Speedwagon Foundation's
messenger wasn't human.
You just didn't even see that
it was here right on time,
weaving through the deadly
rain of frogs like an angel.
It made it to this courtyard.
Savage Guardian is the
name of that pigeon.
And like all trained carrier pigeons, it
will bring the disc to its rightful place.
Hail Snake!
The gun that the guard dropped
earlier is still over near the gate!
Blow that bird out of the sky!
Ugh, idiotic guard!
He completely emptied the clip of bullets!
Damn it!
I won.
Don't underestimate me, you insolent brat!
This changes nothing.
Even with Star Platinum returned,
Your father would be nothing
more than a broken puppet.
He will never be able to recognize
you as his own daughter again.
This little game is over!
Hey look, there's a guard
knocked out over there.
Don't step on the frauds.
And check the courtyard.
There might be someone else.
No, not yet.
I can't faint here.
The stand user has to be nearby somewhere.
I have to find out who
Pale Snake really is.
And the user still has
my father's memory disk.
Now's the best chance I'm gonna
get to discover who they are.
Hey!
Look outside the window!
Oh my god! Unbelievable!
It's a bloody miracle!
But who's gonna clean up this mess?
Nothing has changed at all.
The only reason I stole Star
Platinum in the first place was
to defeat Jotaro Kujo and avenge
the death of my best friend.
What matters most is the memory disk,
and it still remains in my possession.
Everything is going as planned.
The instructions on how to reach Heaven
can only be found in Jotaro's memory.
An abnormal occurrence
where frogs rained down
from the sky solely in
the prison courtyard.
Through the chaos of
this unexplainable event,
Jolene's attempt at
escaping went unquestioned.
And thanks to a feathered friend,
the Speedwagon Foundation
obtained the disc
which contains Jotaro
Kujo's Star Platinum.
However, without the memory disc, Jotaro's
mind and soul will never be restored.
Although you think I cope,
my head is filled with hope.
Of some place
other than here?
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming for all?
From today!
Sports Maximum.
This is the bone that I
want to ask you about.
Using your unique abilities,
there is something I
would like to try really
does that belong to a
human whose bone is it?
That answer is none of your business.
Let's just say it belongs
to an old friend of mine.
The bone of my dear friend.
The great deal.
Thank you.